(サスケ)ねえねえ 兄さん
手裏剣を投げるコツ 教えてよ。
Big Brother, teach me
the trick to throwing shuriken.
(イタチ)俺は忙しい。
I'm busy.
手裏剣なら
父上に習えばいいだろ。
Learn it from Father.
そうさ。
Yeah right!
いつもいつも
忙しい忙しいってさ。
You always say
you're busy this, busy that.
兄さんは 俺のこと
嫌いなんだよ。
You don't like me, do you?
そうだよ
きっと嫌いなんだ。
I knew it. You just don't like me.
Don't say that, Sasuke.
まあ そう言うな サスケ。
I really don't have the time today.
本当に
今日は時間がないんだ。
今日は 今日は。
Today this, today that…
あ～あ 明日は
いったい いつ来るんだか。
When will tomorrow ever come?
許せ サスケ。
I'm sorry, Sasuke.
あ そうだ。
Oh, yeah…
今度 父上たちが
泊まりで出かけるとき→
The next time Father and Mother
go somewhere…
休みがとれるかもしれない。
I may be able to
take some time off.
え 本当？ いつ いつ？
Huh?
Really? When is that?!
父上に聞いておけ
じゃあな。
Ask Father.
See you.
うん。
Uh-huh!
(フガク)これは 何て魚だ
なかなかうまい。
What do you call this fish?
It's really good!
(ミコト)そう？ 今日も
安売りしてたのよ。
Really?
It was on sale today!
旬のものは
何でも安くてうまいのさ。
Things in season are always
cheap and delicious.
(フガク)言うなあ サスケ ハハハ。
Is that right, Sasuke?!
母さん おかわり。
(ミコト)はいはい。
Seconds please, Mom!
Of course.
兄さんから聞いたけど→
Big Brother said
you're going somewhere.
父さんたちが
出かけるのっていつ？
When is that?
(フガク)ああ 母さんの家に
泊まりで行くんだ。
Yes…
We're going to visit
your mother's family.
ふ～ん。
Oh…
(フガク)あいつが
そんなことを お前に。
So he told you, did he?
次の休みの日に
行こうと思うが。
I thought we'd go
on my next day off.
お前も来るか？
Would you like to come?
I'm gonna have Big Brother
teach me all kinds of stuff.
俺は 兄さんに
いろいろ教えてもらうんだ。
あいつが お前に？
He said…he'll teach you?
Yeah! He promised.
うん 約束したんだ。
Itachi did?
(ミコト)イタチがねえ。
珍しいわね。
That's unusual!
はい ご飯。
Here's your rice!
I can help you practice
kunai-throwing too, you know.
クナイなら
私がお稽古してあげるのに。
お稽古じゃない 修業なんだ。
It's not practice, it's training.
あ～ すまない お茶もらえるか。
はい。
– Oh, can I trouble you for some tea?
– Sure!
熱めで頼む。
はいはい。
– Make it hot, too.
– All right!
Now you try it, just like that.
(イタチ)お前も今と同じように。
えい。
サスケ 腕を上げたな。
ヘヘ。
You've improved, Sasuke!
もう母さんより曲げられる。
I can throw better than Mom now.
じゃあ こいつはどうかな？
All right, then how about this?
えっ…。
Huh?
やっぱり兄さんはすごいよ。
You're terrific, Big Brother.
それって どうやるの？
How did you do that?
お前なら すぐ投げられるさ。
You'll start throwing
like that very soon.
お前は俺とよく似てる。
You're a lot like me.
ヘヘ。
兄さん また今日みたいに
教えてよ。
Big Brother… Can you teach me
again sometime, like today?
そうだな 時間が合ったらな。
Sure, when I have the time.
約束だよ。
ああ。
Promise?
Yeah.
お前 うちは一族の
成り立ちのことは知ってるか？
Do you know how
the Uchiha Clan came about?
えっ まだちゃんと
習ってないけど。
What?
I haven't really learned about it
in-depth yet.
うちはの家紋は
誇り高い一族の証しなんだ。
The Uchiha crest is the symbol
and proof of our prestigious clan.
あの うちわの絵が誇り？
An image of a fan…is prestigious?
火をおこすには風がいるだろ？
You need wind
to start a fire, right?
うちわで風を起こすんだ。
You produce wind with a fan.
それって すごいの？
Is that…a great thing?
アハハ まぁ そのうち
わかるときがくる。
Well, you'll understand in time.
兄さんは 一族のために戦う？
Big Brother…
Do you fight for
the sake of the clan?
どうかな？
I wonder…
それは
俺にも まだ わからないんだ。
I'm not sure
about that either just yet.
アハハハ。
よし 今夜は俺が腕を振るうぞ。
All right!
I'm gonna make us a feast tonight!
アチチ！
Ouch! Hot!
これって 兄さんって…。
You made all of this?
うん ちょっと頑張りすぎたかな？
Yeah…
Maybe I went a little overboard.
ちょっと ね。
A little, huh?
苦しい。
I'm stuffed!
おい サスケ 今夜は外で寝ないか？
Hey, Sasuke…
Want to sleep outside tonight?
えっ いいの？ そんなことして。
Are you sure it's okay to do that?
おいおい そんな慌てなくても…。
Hey, don't rush!
痛ぇ。
Oww!
寒くないか？
Are you cold?
ううん 気持いい。
Nope… It feels great.
俺 兄さんみたいな
優秀な忍になって→
I want to become
a skilled shinobi like you,
父さんに認めてほしいんだ。
and win Father's approval.
フフッ 俺みたいだって？
What? Like me?
お前は俺を超えろ。
You will surpass me.
無理 無理。
Impossible.
No way. I mean, you're gifted.
だって 兄さんは天才だもん。
みんな そう言ってるし。
Everyone says so.
アハハ お前は俺に似てる。
You're a lot like me.
可能性はあるさ。
You've got the potential.
じゃあ 超えてやる。
Okay then, I'll surpass you!
(イタチ)サスケ… サスケ…。
Sasuke…
Sasuke?
(フガク)おい サスケ。
Hey…
Sasuke…
お前 こんなとこで何してる？
What are you doing out here?
何ですか？ 父さん…。
What is it?
Father?
えっ… ここは？ なんで？
Huh?
Where am I?
Why—?
あ～ 昨日 兄さんが外でって。
Oh!
Big Brother said
we could sleep outside…
(ミコト)イタチが？ フフフフ…。
Itachi did?
兄さんは どこ？
もう出たみたいだな。
Where's Big Brother?
Seems he's left already.
俺には あいつの考えていることが
よくわからん。
I just don't know
what he's thinking.
兄さん。
Big Brother…
(サクラ)ただいま。
I'm home…
ん～。
ヘヘッ。
うん よし！
All right!
(サクラ)ハハハ。
Should I part it here?
But…
ん～。
ふぅ。
あ～あ～っ！
あ～。
(キザシ)おい サクラ お前→
Hey, Sakura.
Sakura, aren't your bangs
getting in the way?
前髪うっとうしくないのか？
切っちゃえばいいのに。
You should just cut them!
Oh, don't start, dear!
(メブキ)もう お父さんったら…。
女の子はね いろいろあるの。
Girls have their reasons…
そんなこと言うと
サクラに嫌われちゃうわよ。
If you say things like that,
Sakura will start hating you!
ハハハッ ハハハッ。
Oh… You like flowers?
(いの)へぇ あんた
お花が好きなんだ？
えっ 誰？
Who's there?
あっ いのちゃん。
Oh, it's you, Ino.
(いの)コスモスが好きなんだ。
You like cosmos?
Oh…
(サクラ)あ いや… えっと… うん。
Uh…
Yeah.
ほら これ見なよ。 ジャーン！
Take a look!
Tadah!
わぁ～ きれい。
でしょ。
Oh, it's so pretty!
Isn't it?
これで あんたの髪 結ってあげる。
I'll tie your hair up with this.
え？ 私の髪？
Huh? My hair?
サクラは かわいい顔してんだから…。
You're cute Sakura, so…
よしっと。
There!
こっちのほうが断然いいよ。
This is way better!
でも… 私 おでこが。
But…
my forehead is…
A billboard brow…
デコリーン。
それってさ 隠してるから
からかわれるんだよ。
People tease you
because you try to cover it up.
堂々としてればいいの。
そうすれば 周りが変わる。
Just show it off.
Then the people around you
will change.
いのちゃんは 強いから…。
But Ino, you're so strong…
う～ん 絶対こっちのほうが
かわいいと思うけどな。
Well, I think this is much better.
だってさ サクラは
スタイルだっていいんだし→
You've got good style…
I think you should
have more confidence…
もっと自信持って
いいと思うんだよね。
(サクラ)あのね
私 友達ができたんだ。
I…
I made a friend.
山中いのちゃんっていって
すごく かわいくて→
Her name's Ino Yamanaka
and she's cute, strong,
fashionable, and kind…
強くて おしゃれで 優しくて…。
そっか サクラに友達か…。
I see.
You made a friend, Sakura?
If she's cute,
I'd like to meet her too.
そんなにかわいいなら
お父さんも会いたいな。
(メブキ)もう お父さんったら。
Oh, dear…
What are you saying!
なに言ってんだか。
サクラ よかったね。
お友達は大切にするんだよ。
I'm happy for you, Sakura.
You must cherish your friends.
友達はね
大切な人生の財産だからね。
Friends are precious
assets in life.
うん。
Okay!
Ino gave me this ribbon.
このリボン いのちゃんがくれたの。
(キザシ)すっごく似合ってるぞ！
It looks great on you.
母さんの若い頃みたいに
かわいいぞ！
You're as cute as Mom was
when she was young.
まぁ… お父さんったら
かわいいだなんて！
Oh dear… You said I'm cute?
ハハハ！ サクラ ついでに
彼氏もできたりしてな。
Sakura…while you're at it,
you should find a boyfriend.
Come on, Dad!
(サクラ)お父さんの バカ！
(キザシ)アハハハハハ！
Wow… That's amazing.
(いの)へぇ～！ すごいね。
これ 全部 サクラが１人でやったの？
You did this all by yourself?
It's nothing at all!
(サクラ)全然 すごくないよ！
私 いのちゃんみたいに
センスよくないし。
I'm not creative like you.
う～ん このコスモス…。
See this cosmos?
To bring out its beauty,
(いの)コスモスを活かすなら
周りを それに合わせるのよ。
the things around it
should complement it,
お互いが ぶつからないようにね。
so that they don't clash.
よ～し！
All right…
ちょっと 生けてみるね。
I'm going to rearrange them a bit.
Umm, I'll do this…
えっと… こんな感じに
ここを こうして…。
And do this…
あのね…。
You know…
私… 好きな人ができたんだ。
…there's a boy I like.
へぇ～！ 知らなかった。
ん～ 誰かな？
Really? I didn't know.
Who is it?
最近 サクラが明るくなったのは
そのせいかな？
Is that why you've been
more cheerful lately?
よし！ 完成。
Okay, all done!
いや
そういうわけじゃないんだけど。
Not really…
サスケ君が…。
but Sasuke…
そうなんだ… サスケ君ね。
I see…
It's Sasuke?
サスケ君
長い髪の人が好きなんだって。
I heard Sasuke likes girls
with long hair.
だからね 私も…。
あ～！ ごめん。
So I was…
Oh, sorry.
私 用事 思い出しちゃった。
また来るね。
I just remembered something.
I'll come again later.
Huh? Ino…
えっ？ いのちゃん！
あ… 今日は ありがとう！
Thank you for today.
ねぇ ねぇ！
最近さ サクラ 明るくなったよね。
Hey…
そうかな。
あれ… いのって
サクラと仲よかったんじゃないの？
別に。
ふ～ん。
(サクラ)サスケ君。
私 あなたのことが…。
なんだ？
お前… 誰？
うわ… うわぁ うわ～っ！
(ナルト)どうしたのかな？ あの子。
廊下は
走っちゃいけないんだってばよ。
はぁ～！
しゃ～んなろ～！
うわ～っ！
す… すげぇ女の子だってばよ。